Three fast guns against one determined man!
Shoot Out is a western film directed by Henry Hathaway.
Clay Lomax, a bank robber, gets out of jail after an 7 year sentence.
He is looking after Sam Foley, the man who betrayed him.
Knowing that, Foley hires three men to pay attention of Clay's steps.
The things get complicated when Lomax, waiting to receive some money from his ex-lover, gets only the notice
of her death and an 7 year old girl, sometimes very annoying, presumed to be his daughter.
Clay Lomax, played by Gregory Peck.
Juliana, played by Patricia Quinn.
Bobby Jay, played by Robert F. Lyons.
Alma, played by Susan Tyrrell.
Trooper, played by Jeff Corey.
Sam Foley, played by James Gregory.
Shoot Out is a 1971 American Western film directed by
Henry Hathaway and starring Gregory Peck.
The film is adapted from Will James's 1930 novel, The Lone Cowboy.
The film was produced, directed, and written by the team that
delivered the Oscar-winning film True Grit.
This was the second-to-last of the 65 films directed by Hathaway.
The film explores themes of gunslinger, based on novel or
book, chase, kidnapping, release from prison.